Guide to the Edmund Clarence Stedman Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, Manuscripts, and Diaries
  - Read, Thomas Buchanan (Box 122)
  - Read, Carrie L. (Box 122)
  - Read, John Meredith (Box 122)
  - Redfield, Julia H. (Box 122)
  - Reed, F.H.W. (Box 122)
  - Reed, Nelson P., & Co. (Box 122)
  - Reese, Lizette Woodworth (Box 122)
  - Reese, Minnie E. (Box 122)
  - Reeves, Frank J (Box 122)
  - Reich, Jacques (Box 123)
  - Reid, Anna Odlin (Box 123)
  - Reid, Elizabeth Mills (Box 123)
  - Reid, Margus (Box 123)
  - Reid, Mary J (Box 123)
  - Reid, Robert A (Box 123)
  - Reid, Whitelaw (Box 123)
  - Remann, Mary J (Box 124)
  - Remsen, Ira (Box 124)
  - Repplier, Agnes (Box 124)
  - Rhead, Louis John (Box 124)
  - Rhees, Bessie (Box 124)
  - Rhoads, James E (Box 124)
  - Rhodes, Albert (Box 124)
  - Rhodes, Harrison Garfield (Box 124)
  - Rhodes, James Ford (Box 124)
  - Rhys, Arthur (Box 124)
  - Rhys,. Ernest Percival (Box 124)
  - Rhys, Grace Little (Box 124)
  - Rice, Allen Thorndike (Box 125)
  - Rice, Wallace de Groot Cecil (Box 125)
  - Rich, Charles T (Box 125)
  - Rich Hirem (Box 125)
  - Richards, Laura Elizabeth Howe (Box 125)
  - Richards, William Rogers (Box 125)
  - Richardson, Abby Sage McFarland (Box 125)
  - Richardson, Charles Francis (Box 125)
  - Richardson, Elizabeth Miner Thomas (Box 125)
  - Rickey, Nellie (Box 125)
  - Riddle, George (Box 125)
  - Rideal, Charles (Box 125)
  - Rideing, William Henry (Box 125)
  - Rider, Sidney S (Box 125)
  - Rigg, N.M. (Box 125)
  - Riggs, Arthur Stanley (Box 125)
  - Riker,.Thad W. (Box 125)
  - Riley, James Whitcomb (Box 125)
  - Riley, Morgan Thomas (Box 125)
  - Riordan, Roger (Box 125)
  - Ripley, Hannah Lothrop (Box 125)
  - Ritter, F.G. (Box 125)
  - Riverside Press (Box 125)
  - Rives, George Lockhart (Box 125)
  - Robb, Ellie D. (Box 126)
  - Robbins, Howard Chandler (Box 126)
  - Robbins, W.S. (Box 126)
  - Robert, Christopher Rhinelander (Box 126)
  - Roberts, Charles George Douglas (Box 126)
  - Roberts, Donald A. (Box 126)
  - Roberts, Edwards (Box 126)
  - Roberts, Theodore (Box 126)
  - Roberts Brothers (Box 126)
  - Robertson, F.N. (Box 126)
  - Robertson, Harrison (Box 126)
  - Robinson, Alexander C (Box 126)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington (Box 126)
  - Robinson, Henry C (Box 126)
  - Robinson, Louise B (Box 126)
  - Robinson, Lucy Catlin Bull (Box 126)
  - Robinson, Mary Webster (Box 126)
  - Robinson, Tracy (1875-1892 & n.d.) (Box 127)
  - Robinson, Tracy (1893-1909 & mss.) (Box 128)
  - Roche, James Jeffery (Box 129)
  - Rood, (Sir) Rennell (Box 129)
  - Rogers, James E.T. (Box 129)
  - Rogé, Charlotte Fiske Bates (Box 129)
  - Rogers, Abner (Box 129)
  - Rogers, Beatrice Roberts (Box 129)
  - Rogers, C.H. Bulkeley (Box 129)
  - Rogers, Joseph Morgan (Box 129)
  - Rogers, Robert Cameron (Box 129)
  - Rohlfs, Charles (Box 129)
  - Rolfe, Frederick William (Corvo) (Box 129)
  - Rollins, Clice Marland Wellington (Box 129)
  - Rollins, Daniel. M (Box 129)
  - Rome, T.H. (Box 129)
  - Romeike, Henry (Box 129)
  - Rooney, John Jerome (Box 129)
  - Root, A.P. (Box 129)
  - Rose, Heloise Durant (Box 130)
  - Rose, Roy Clarke (Box 130)
  - Roseboro, Viola (Box 130)
  - Rosenkrans, Baron (Box 130)
  - Rosenthal, Albert (Box 130)
  - Robert, Otto Arthur (Box 130)
  - Rowe, H.B. (Box 130)
  - Rowell, Myra S (Box 130)
  - Rowland, Orlando (Box 130)
  - Rudd, Jean Porter (Box 130)
  - Runkle, Bertha (Box 130)
  - Runkle, Mrs Lucia Gilbert (Box 130)
  - Russell, Horace (Box 130)
  - Rutherford, Mildred Le14B (Box 130)
  - Rutledge,. C.A. (Box 130)
  - J. Sabin's Son (Box 131)
  - Sage, Margaret Olivia Slocum (Box 131)
  - St. Clair, H.H. (Box 131)
  - Saint Guadens, Homer (Box 131)
  - Saint, John, Mrs. Cynthia Morgan (Box 131)
  - St. Righter, C. Lester (Box 131)
  - Salt, Henry Stephens (Box 131)
  - Saltus, Edgar Evertson (Box 131)
  - Saltus, Francis H (Box 131)
  - Sampson, Virginia O (Box 131)
  - Sanborn, Francis Fenton (Box 131)
  - Sanborn, Franklin Benjamin' (Box 131)
  - Sanborn, Kate (Box 131)
  - Sandley, F.A. (Box 131)
  - Sanford, Edward I (Box 131)
  - Sanford, Orlin Mead (Box 131)
  - Sanger, George P (Box 131)
  - Sangster, Margaret E. (Box 131)
  - Sargent, Franklin Hoven (Box 131)
  - Savage, Charles E (Box 131)
  - Savage, James W (Box 131)
  - Savage, Minet Judson (Box 131)
  - Savary, John (Box 131)
  - Sawyer, Charles Carroll (Box 131)
  - Sawyer, Mildred Conway (Box 131)
  - Saxe, John Godfrey (Box 131)
  - Saxton, Andrew Rice (Box 131)
  - Scally, J.W. (Box 132)
  - Scarff, Charles W. (Box 132)
  - Schaefer, Florence Moulton (Box 132)
  - Schaff, Philip (Box 132)
  - Schaffauer, Herman George (Box 132)
  - Schelling, Felix Emanuel (Box 132)
  - Schiliemann, Heinrich (Box 132)
  - Schnitzer, William M (Box 132)
  - Schollast, The (Box 132)
  - Schott, Margaret Ridgely (Box 132)
  - Schreiber & Sans (Box 132)
  - Schuckers, Jacob W (Box 132)
  - Schuyler, Montgomery (Box 132)
  - Scollard, Clinton (Box 132)
  - Scott, Duncan Campbell (Box 132)
  - Scott, Frederick George (Box 132)
  - Scott Frank Hall (Box 132)
  - Scott, John G (Box 132)
  - Scott, Leonora Cranch (Box 132)
  - Scouller, .J.N. (Box 132)
  - Scribner, Charles (Box 132)
  - Scribner, John Blair (Box 132)
  - Scudder, Grace Owen (Box 132)
  - Scudder, Horace Elisha (Box 132)
  - Scudder, W.S. (Box 132)
  - Searing, Esther L. (Box 133)
  - Searing, Mrs. Laura Catherine (Box 133)
  - Secor, David Pell (Box 133)
  - Sedgewick, Frederick (Box 133)
  - Seligman, DeWitt J. (Box 133)
  - Seligman, Issac Newton (Box 133)
  - Selmser, E.P. (Box 133)
  - Selmser, Mary D (Box 133)
  - Seton, Ernest Thompson (Box 133)
  - Sewall, Frank (Box 133)
  - Shaler, Nathaniel Southgate (Box 133)
  - Shanks, William Franklin Gore (Box 133)
  - Sharp, Elizabeth Amelia Sharp (Box 133)
  - Sharp, Evelyn (Box 133)
  - Sharp, Henry T. (Box 133)
  - Sharp, William (Box 134)
  - Sharpe, P.T.. (Box 134)
  - Sharpe, Robert D (Box 134)
  - Shaw, Albert (Box 134)
  - Shaw, Wilson A. (Box 134)
  - Shea, John Gilman (Box 134)
  - Shedd, William Greenough Thayer (Box 134)
  - Shelding, Susie B. (Box 134)
  - Sheldon, G.H. (Box 134)
  - Sheldon, George Hilliam (Box 134)
  - Sheldon, James, Jr. (Box 134)
  - Sheldon & Company (Box 134)
  - Shepard, Elliott F. (Box 134)
  - Sherman, Francis (Box 134)
  - Sherman, Frank Dempster (Box 134)
  - Sherwood, Mary Elizabeth Wilson (Box 134)
  - Shields, James (Box 135)
  - Shillaber, Benjamin Penhailow (Box 135)
  - Shinn, Charles Howard (Box 135)
  - Shinn, Millicent Washburn (Box 135)
  - Shipman, Carolyn (Box 135)
  - Shiras, George, Jr. (Box 135)
  - Shryock, Eula Mae (Box 135)
  - Shugio, H (Box 135)
  - Shumaid, L. Frank (Box 135)
  - Shunk, James F. (Box 135)
  - Shurtleff, Clara Dwight (Box 135)
  - Shurtleff, William Steele (Box 135)
  - Sickel, David Banks (Box 135)
  - Simonds, May (Box 135)
  - Simpson, John J (Box 135)
  - Sims, William Sowden (Box 135)
  - Sinclair, May (Box 135)
  - Skinner, Charles Montgomery (Box 135)
  - Sladen, Douglas Brooke Wheelton (Box 135)
  - Sladen, Margaret Isabel Muirhead (Box 135)
  - Slason Thompson &Co. (Box 135)
  - Slaughter, P. (Box 135)
  - Slicer, Thomas Roberts (Box 136)
  - Sloan, William Milligan (Box 136)
  - Slassum, Annie T. (Box 136)
  - Small, Herbert (Box 136)
  - Sally, George Washburn (Box 136)
  - Smalley, Phillips (Box 136)
  - Smalley, Phoebe (Box 136)
  - Smallwood, John J. (Box 136)
  - Smart, Lizzie Parker (Box 136)
  - Smillie, James David (Box 137)
  - Smith, Azariah (Box 137)
  - Smith, Belle E. (Box 137)
  - Smith, Benjamin Eli (Box 137)
  - Smith, Carrie A. (Box 137)
  - Smith, Edward Delafield (Box 137)
  - Smith, Edward J (Box 137)
  - Smith, Elizabeth Oakes Prince (Box 137)
  - Smith, Emily B. (Box 137)
  - Smith, Francis Hopkinson (Box 137)
  - Smith, Frances Louisa (Box 137)
  - Smith, Frank P (Box 137)
  - Smith, George Barnett (Box 137)
  - Smith, Gerrit (Box 137)
  - Smith, Harold V (Box 137)
  - Smith, Harry Bache (Box 137)
  - Smith, Helen Evertson (Box 137)
  - Smith, J.S. (Box 137)
  - Smith, .J. Sumner (Box 137)
  - Smith, Jeanie Oliver Davidson (Box 137)
  - Smith, John Cotton (Box 137)
  - Smith, Lloyd Pearsall (Box 137)
  - Smith, Marion Stuart (Box 137)
  - Smith, Mary Stuart Waite (Box 137)
  - Smith, Matton Meier (Box 137)
  - Smith, May Riley (Box 137)
  - Smith, Minna Caroline (Box 137)
  - Smith, Munroe (Box 137)
  - Smith, Pauline A (Box 137)
  - Smith, Reginald John (Box 137)
  - Smith, Roswell (Box 137)
  - Smith, S. Decatur, Jr. (Box 137)
  - Smith, Shirley "'. (Box 137)
  - Smith, Walter George (Box 137)
  - Snider, Denton .J (Box 138)
  - Solberg, Thorvald (Box 138)
  - Soule, Leslie (Box 138)
  - Southwick, Albert Plympton (Box 138)
  - Souvakolb, Franklin S (Box 138)
  - Spalding, J.A. (Box 138)
  - Spalding, James R. (Box 138)
  - Spencer, Isidore (Box 138)
  - Sperry, Watson Robertson (Box 138)
  - Spindler,.John F (Box 138)
  - Spofford, Ainsworth Rand (Box 138)
  - Spofford, Ellen B (Box 138)
  - Spofford, Harriet Prescott (Box 138)
  - Sproul, George D (Box 138)
  - Spruance, Presley (Box 138)
  - Squire, Mary E. (Box 138)
  - Stager, Anson (Box 138)
  - Starin, Henry Gaylord (Box 138)
  - Starrett, Helen E (Box 138)
  - Stearns, Henry Putman (Box 138)
  - Stedman, Arthur Griffin (Box 138)
  - Stedman, C .M. (Box 139)
  - Stedman, Calvin A. (Box 139)
  - Stedman, Charles Ellery (Box 139)
  - Stedman, Charles Frederick (Box 139)
  - Stedman, Edmund Burke (Box 139)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1849-1862 & n.d.) (Box 140)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1863-1875) (Box 141)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1876-1881) (Box 142)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1882-1885) (Box 143)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1886-1888) (Box 144)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1889-1891) (Box 145)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1892-1897) (Box 146)
  - Stedman, Edmund C. (1898-1907) (Box 147)
  - Stedman, Elizabeth S (Box 147)
  - Stedman, Ellen Montague Douglas (Box 147)
  - Stedman, Frederick Stuart (Box 148)
  - Stedman, George T (Box 148)
  - Stedman, Griffin (Box 148)
  - Stedman, Helen E (Box 148)
  - Stedman, James (Box 148)
  - Stedman, Laura Hyde Woodworth (Mrs Edmund C. J (Box 148)
  - Stedman, Linda Edevene Wadman (Box 148)
  - Stedman, Mary A (Box 148)
  - Stedman, Mary E (Box 148)
  - Stedman, R.H. (Box 148)
  - Stedman, Thomas Lathrop (Box 148)
  - Steele, Frederick M (Box 148)
  - Steele, Zulma DeLacy Dorr (Box 148)
  - Stein, Evaleen (Box 148)
  - Steinback, Josef (Box 148)
  - Stephens, Kate (Box 148)
  - Stephens, Louis H (Box 148)
  - Sterling, Ada (Box 149)
  - Sterling, Joseph H (Box 149)
  - Sterner, Albert (Box 149)
  - Sterry, Ruth (Box 149)
  - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin (Box 149)
  - Stevens, Charles Ellis (Box 149)
  - Stevens, John Austin, Jr. (Box 149)
  - Stevenson, Edward Irenaeus Prime (Box 149)
  - Stevenson, Mary Elizabeth carter (Box 149)
  - Stewart, Alexander (Box 149)
  - Stewart, George W (Box 149)
  - Stewart, James M (Box 149)
  - Stewart, William M (Box 149)
  - Stierlin, F.C. (Box 149)
  - Stillman, Annie R (Box 149)
  - Stilwell, Walter L (Box 149)
  - Stimson, Daniel MacMartin (Box 149)
  - Stisted, Clotilda Elizabet~ (Box 149)
  - Stockard, Henry Jerome (Box 149)
  - Stockbridge, George, H (Box 149)
  - Stockbridge, J.C. (Box 149)
  - Stockton, Frank R (Box 149)
  - Stockton, Nan S. (Box 149)
  - Stoddard, Charles Augustus (Box 149)
  - Stansbury, E.A. (Box 149)
  - Stoddard, Charles Warren (Box 149)
  - Stanton, Frank Lebby (Box 149)
  - Stanton, Theodore (Box 149)
  - Starey, A.B. (Box 149)
  - Stoddard, Ellzabeth Drew Barstow [n.y.] (Box 150)
  - Stoddard, Ellzabeth Drew Barstow [n.y.] (Box 151)
  - Stoddard, Ellzabeth Drew Barstow (1860-1902) (Box 152)
  - Stoddard, Francis Hovey (Box 153)
  - Stoddard, Joseph Marshall (Box 153)
  - Stoddard, Lorimer (Box 153)
  - Stoddard, Lucy M. Smith (Box 153)
  - Stoddard, Richard Henry (Box 153)
  - Stoddard, William Osborn (Box 154)
  - Stokes, Frederick A & Co. (Box 154)
  - Stokes, Frederick Abbot (Box 154)
  - Stokes, James (Box 154)
  - Stokes, James Graham Phelps (Box 154)
  - Stone, & Kimball (Box 154)
  - Stone, Electa B. Woodworth (Box 154)
  - Stone, Frederick Dawson (Box 154)
  - Stone, Frederick J (Box 154)
  - Stone, Herbert Stuart (Box 154)
  - Stone, M.A. (Box 154)
  - Storey, Moorfield (Box 154)
  - Stratton, Albert E (Box 154)
  - Streamer, Volney (Box 154)
  - Street, Mrs. T.C. (Box 154)
  - Strickland, Edward. F (Box 154)
  - Strohm, Gertrude (Box 154)
  - Strong, Samuel A (Box 154)
  - Stuart, Ruth McEnery (Box 154)
  - Sturgis, Russell (Box 154)
  - Sullivan, Algernon S (Box 155)
  - Sullivan, James Frank (Box 155)
  - Sumner, George (Box 155)
  - Sutliff, Mary Louisa (Box 155)
  - Sutphen, William Gilbert van Tassel (Box 155)
  - Sutro, Theodore (Box 155)
  - Swayne, H. Marshall (Box 155)
  - Sweet, Emelie Tracy Y (Box 155)
  - Sweet, Estelle C.R. (Box 155)
  - Sweetser, M.F. (Box 155)
  - Swetser, Henry Edward (Box 155)
  - Swinburne, Lewis (Box 155)
  - Swing, David (Box 155)
  - Tabb, John Banister (Box 155)
  - Taft, William Howard (Box 155)
  - Tanner, Merle A (Box 155)
  - Tarkington, Booth (Box 155)
  - Tassin, Algernon de Vivier (Box 155)
  - Tatman, Charles T (Box 155)
  - Tatnall, Frances Dorr Swift (Box 155)
  - Tauchert, O (Box 155)
  - Taylor, Bayard (Box 155)
  - Taylor, Charles Edward (Box 155)
  - Taylor, Douglas (Box 155)
  - Taylor, Frederick (Box 155)
  - Taylor, James Monroe (Box 155)
  - Taylor, Joseph Russell (Box 155)
  - Taylor, Marie Hansen (Mrs Bayard) 1878-1890 & n.d.) (Box 156)
  - Taylor, Marie Hansen (Mrs Bayard) 1891-1915) (Box 157)
  - Taylor, Rebecca Bauerway (Box 158)
  - Teall, Gardner Callahan (Box 158)
  - Teller, Helen Kane (Box 158)
  - Templeton, James M. (Box 158)
  - Terhune, Mary Virginia (Box 158)
  - Terry, Edmund R (Box 158)
  - Terry,·Luther (Box 158)
  - Thacher, Thomas A (Box 158)
  - Thaxter, John (Box 158)
  - Thaxter, Roland (Box 158)
  - Thayer, Caroline C. Woodworth (Box 158)
  - Thayer, Charles F (Box 158)
  - Thayer, Stephen Henry (Box 158)
  - Thayer, William Roscoe (Box 158)
  - Thiebes-Stierlin Music Co (Box 158)
  - Thomas, Calvin (Box 158)
  - Thomas, Charles L (Box 158)
  - Thomas, Edith M (Box 158)
  - Thomas, Frances Melville (Box 158)
  - Thomas, Henry W (Box 158)
  - Thomas, James Carey (Box 158)
  - Thomas, Jessie B (Box 158)
  - Thomas, Martha Carey (Box 158)
  - Thomas, William Moy (Box 158)
  - Thompson, Daniel Greenleaf (Box 158)
  - Thompson, Henrietta G (Box 158)
  - Thompson, Hill H (Box 158)
  - Thompson, M.L. (Box 158)
  - Thompson, Slason (Box 158)
  - Thresher, Caliste P. (Box 158)
  - Tibbits, Henry (Box 158)
  - Ticknor, Benjamin Holt (1869-1883) (Box 159)
  - Ticknor, Benjamin Holt (1884-1905) (Box 160)
  - Ticknor, Caroline (Box 161)
  - Ticknor & Co. (Box 161)
  - Ticknor & Fields (Box 161)
  - Tidlen, Douglas (Box 161)
  - Tileson, Mary Wilder (Box 161)
  - Tilletson, H.R. (Box 161)
  - Tilley, William James (Box 161)
  - Timmins, George (Box 161)
  - Tinckam, Charles William. (Box 161)
  - Tincker, Mary Agnes (Box 161)
  - Titcomb, Virginia C (Box 161)
  - Titterton, John (Box 161)
  - Todd, Charles Burr (Box 162)
  - Todd, Mabel Loomis (Box 162)
  - Toland, Mary B. Morrison Gridley (Box 162)
  - Tooker, Lewis Frank (Box 162)
  - Torrans, Beauregard (Box 162)
  - Torrence, F.D. (Box 162)
  - Torrence, Ridgely (Box 162)
  - Tourneur, Nigel (Box 162)
  - Towle, George Makepeace (Box 162)
  - Towne, Charles Hanson (Box 162)
  - Townsend, Annie Lake (Box 162)
  - Townsend, George Alfred (Box 162)
  - Townsend, George Washington (Box 162)
  - Townsend, John Wilson (Box 162)
  - Townsend, Mary Ashley (Box 162)
  - Townsend, S. DeLancey (Box 162)
  - Tracy, George M. (Box 163)
  - Trask, Kate Nichols (Box 163)
  - Trask, Spencer (Box 163)
  - Traubel, Horace Logo (Box 163)
  - Tredwell, Daniel M (Box 163)
  - Trench, Alfred Cnenevix (Box 163)
  - Trent, William Peterfield (Box 163)
  - Triggs, Oscar L (Box 163)
  - Trollope, Theodosia Garrow (Box 163)
  - Troubetzkoy, Amelie Rives (Box 163)
  - Trumbull, Annie Eliot (Box 163)
  - Trumbull, Henry Clay (Box 163)
  - Trumbull, James Hammond (Box 163)
  - Trumbull, Jonathan (Box 163)
  - Tucker, Gilbert Milligan (Box 164)
  - Tucker, Margaret Lucinda: Smith Burr (Box 164)
  - Tucker, Mary Margaretta (Box 164)
  - Tucker, Willis Gaylord (Box 164)
  - Tupper Edith Sessions (Box 164)
  - Turnbull, Frencese Hubbard Litchfield (Box 164)
  - Turnbull, Lawrence (Box 164)
  - Turner, Emory S. (Box 164)
  - Twichell, Joseph Hopkins (Box 165)
  - Twining, Kinsley (Box 165)
  - Twombly, Alexander Stevenson (Box 165)
  - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 165)
  - Tyler, William Royall (Box 165)
  - Underhill, Edward Fitch (Box 165)
  - Underhill, Wilbur (Box 165)
  - Upham, Caroline Ely (Box 165)
  - Upshaw, William D (Box 165)
  - Upward, Al1en (Box 165)
  - Urmy, Clarence Thomas (Box 165)
  - Va1dstein, Charles (Box 166)
  - Vail, Ellen Sitgreaves (Box 166)
  - Valentine, Almira H (Box 166)
  - Valentine, Benjamin Benton (Box 166)
  - Valentine, Edward Abram Uffington (Box 166)
  - Van Arminge, John Howard (Box 166)
  - Van de Hater, Virginia Belie Terhune (Box 166)
  - Van De Water, George Roe (Box 166)
  - Van Dyke, Henry (Box 166)
  - Van Noppen, Leonard Charles (Box 166)
  - Van Rensselaer, Mariana Giswold (Box 166)
  - Van Rensselaer, Peyton (Box 166)
  - Van Schaich, J.D. (Box 166)
  - Van Schaick, S. (Box 166)
  - Van Vorst, Bessie McGinnis (Box 166)
  - Van Vorst, Marie (Box 166)
  - Van Wagenen, Bleecker (Box 166)
  - Van Zile, Edward Sims (Box 166)
  - Vanamee, Grace Davis (Box 166)
  - Vanderbilt, John (Box 166)
  - Vanderpoel, Char1es S (Box 166)
  - Vaughan, John M. (Box 166)
  - Vaughan, Virginia (Box 166)
  - Vaux, Downing (Box 166)
  - Vedder, Elihu (Box 166)
  - Venable, Emerson (Box 166)
  - Venable, William Henry (Box 166)
  - Vernum, James M. (Box 166)
  - Verster, J.T. (Box 166)
  - Vielé, Egbert Lucovickus (Box 166)
  - Villard, Helen Franes Garrison (Box 166)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison (Box 166)
  - Vincent, John Heyl (Box 166)
  - Vincent, Marvin Richardson (Box 166)
  - Vincent, Sarah A Strong (Box 166)
  - Volde, V (Box 166)
  - Wack, Henry Wellington (Box 167)
  - Wager, Charles H.A. (Box 167)
  - Waite, Henry Randall (Box 167)
  - Wakeman, Edgar L. (Box 167)
  - Walker, Francis A (Box 167)
  - Walker, John Brisben (Box 167)
  - Walker, M. Elizabeth C. (Box 167)
  - Wallace, Alfred Russell (Box 167)
  - Wallace, Lewis (Box 167)
  - Wallihan, George P (Box 167)
  - Wallis, Severn Taackle (Box 167)
  - Walter, James (Box 167)
  - Walter, Moritz (Box 167)
  - Walter, Rose (Box 167)
  - Walworlh, Jeannetee Ritchie Haldeman (Box 167)
  - Ward, A.C. (Box 167)
  - Ward, Anna Lydia (Box 167)
  - Ward, John Quincy Adams (Box 167)
  - Ward, Samuel (Box 167)
  - Ward, Susan Hayes (Box 167)
  - Ward, William Hayes (Box 167)
  - Wardlaw, George Addison (Box 167)
  - Wardlaw, Josephine Griswold Clark (Box 167)
  - Ware, Eugene Fitch (Box 167)
  - Warfield, Clara C (Box 167)
  - Warner, Charles Dudley (Box 167)
  - Warner, George H (Box 167)
  - Warner, L.B. (Box 167)
  - Welch, Caroline C (Box 167)
  - Wiallis, George B. (Box 167)
  - Warrent Fred Ela. (Box 168)
  - Warren, George William (Box 168)
  - Warren, Ina Russelle (Box 168)
  - Warren, William Fiarfield (Box 168)
  - Wason, C.S. (Box 168)
  - Wason, H.L. (Box 168)
  - Watrous, Charles (Box 168)
  - Watson, Annah Robinson (Box 168)
  - Watson, Edward Willard (Box 168)
  - Watson, (Sir) William (Box 168)
  - Watterson, Henry (Box 168)
  - Watts, Harvey M (Box 168)
  - Watts-Dunton, Halter Theodore (Box 168)
  - Waugh, Arthur (Box 168)
  - Way, H. Irving (Box 168)
  - Wayland, John Elton (Box 168)
  - Webb, Charles Henry (Box 168)
  - Webb, Elizabeth Holden (Box 168)
  - Webb, Richard (Box 168)
  - Webling, Ethel (Box 169)
  - Webling, Lucy (Box 169)
  - Webling, Rosalind, Peggy and Lucy (Box 169)
  - Webster, Alice (Box 169)
  - Webster, Charles L (Box 169)
  - Weeden, Howard (Box 169)
  - Weeks, Charles M (Box 169)
  - Weeks, Stephen Beauregard (Box 169)
  - Weidemeyer, John William (Box 169)
  - Weir, John Ferguson (Box 169)
  - Welles, Edward (Box 169)
  - Welling, James Clarke (Box 169)
  - Wells, Carolyn (Box 169)
  - Wells, Herbert George (Box 169)
  - Welsh, A.H. (Box 169)
  - Wendell, Barrett (Box 170)
  - Wendell, Evert Jansen (Box 170)
  - Wendell, Mrs J.T. (Box 170)
  - Wentz, Virginia Leila (Box 170)
  - Werner Company, Chicago (Box 170)
  - Weston, Theodore (Box 170)
  - Wetmore, Elizabeth Risland (Box 170)
  - Wharton, Edith Newbold Jones (Box 170)
  - Wheeler, Edward Jewitt (Box 170)
  - Wheeler, N.A. (Box 170)
  - Whelpley, A.H. (Box 170)
  - Whicher, George Meason (Box 170)
  - White, .Henna M Bruton (Box 170)
  - White, Alexina Black Mease (Box 170)
  - White, Andrew Dickson (Box 170)
  - White, Charles Trumbull (Box 170)
  - White, Erskine Norman (Box 170)
  - White, Eugene Richard (Box 170)
  - White, Gleeson (Box 170)
  - White, Greenough (Box 170)
  - White, Horace (Box 171)
  - White, James Terry (Box 171)
  - White, Mary A Dodge (Box 171)
  - White, Michael Gifford (Box 171)
  - White, Norman (Box 171)
  - White, Richard Grant (Box 171)
  - White, Stanford (Box 171)
  - White, Stephen Van Culen (Box 171)
  - White, Theodore F (Box 171)
  - Whiteing, Richard (Box 171)
  - Whitelook, Louise Clarkson (Box 171)
  - Whiting, Charles Goodrich (Box 172)
  - Whiting, Lilian (Box 172)
  - Whiting, Valentina Verrier (Box 172)
  - Whiting, W. (Box 172)
  - Whitlock, Genevieve Halè (Box 173)
  - Whitney, Adeline Dutton Train (Box 173)
  - Whitney, Hattie (Box 173)
  - Whitney, Joseph Ernest (Box 173)
  - Whiton, James Morris (Box 173)
  - Whittier, John Greenleaf (Box 173)
  - Whittier Home Association of Amesbury (Box 173)
  - Whittlesey, Mills (Box 173)
  - Whitty, James Howard (Box 173)
  - Wickersham, William F (Box 173)
  - Wickham, N.C. (Box 173)
  - Wiggin, J.H. (Box 173)
  - Wiggin, Kate Douglas (Box 173)
  - Wilbour, Charlotte B. (Box 173)
  - Wlilcox, Asher H (Box 173)
  - Wilcox, Ella Wheeler (Box 173)
  - Wiley, Frances (Box 173)
  - Wilkeson, Samuel (Box 173)
  - Wilkinson, S. Gertrude (Box 173)
  - Wilkinson, William Cleaver (Box 173)
  - Willard, Andrew Jackson (Box 173)
  - Willets, Gilson (Box 173)
  - Willets, Maria (Box 173)
  - Williams, A.P (Box 173)
  - Williams, Alice L (Box 173)
  - Williams, Amy Reeve (Box 173)
  - Williams, Francis Churchill (Box 174)
  - Williams, Francis Howard (Box 174)
  - Willams, .Jesse Lynch (Box 174)
  - Williams, Mary Beatrice Houston (Box 174)
  - Williams, T.M. (Box 174)
  - Williams, Tallcott (Box 174)
  - Willing, John Thomson (Box 174)
  - Willis, Cornelia Grinnell (Box 174)
  - Willis, John A. (Box 174)
  - Willison, Albert D. (Box 174)
  - Wilshire, Henry Gaylord (Box 174)
  - Wilshire, Mary McReynolds (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Alexander C (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Annie E (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Mrs. Arthur (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Arthur E (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Augusta Jane Evans (Box 174)
  - Wilson, F.M. (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Epihpanius (Box 174)
  - Wilson, F.T. (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Floyd Baker (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Francis (Box 174)
  - Wilson, George (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Hickman (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Hiram Henry (Box 174)
  - Wilson, James Grant (Box 174)
  - Wilson, John, and Son (Box 174)
  - Wilson, John G (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Lavinia Rose (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Oliver (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Robert Burns (Box 174)
  - Wilson, Woodrow (Box 174)
  - Wilstach, John Augustine (Box 174)
  - Winchell, Alexander (Box 175)
  - Winchell, J.M. (Box 175)
  - Wingate, Charles Frederick (Box 175)
  - Winsor, .Justin (Box 175)
  - Winter, Elsie Leslie (Box 175)
  - Winter, Jefferson (Box 175)
  - Winter, William (Box 175)
  - Wister, Annie Lee (Box 176)
  - Wister, Owen (Box 176)
  - Woffindin, James (Box 176)
  - Wood, John Seymour (Box 176)